(heavy metal rock plays)
(indistinct chatter)
(band singing indistinctly)
♪ ...You weren't in my corner
♪ You weren't on my side
♪ When times are rough
♪ You hit below the belt
♪ Now it's time-out, baby
♪ When they've rung the bell
♪ I'm not a fighter
I'm a lover ♪
♪ But if you run
Then run for cover ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
(instrumental break)
(feedback whines)
♪ When it's round two, girl...
Turn the... up! Now!
Good.
♪ I get a knockout punch
♪ Or do you start real slow?
(screaming)
♪ I know when
I count you down from 10 ♪
♪ I'll find you in
My lovin' arms again ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah!
♪ When times are rough
♪ You hit below the belt
♪ Now it's time-out, baby
♪ When they've rung the bell
♪ I'm not a fighter
I'm a lover ♪
♪ But if you run
Then run for cover ♪
♪ Fight for your love, yeah
(playing wild solo)
♪ I'm not a fighter
I'm a lover ♪
♪ But if you run
Then run for cover ♪
♪ Fight for your love, yeah!
(women hooting)
(glass breaking)
(groans)
(audience murmuring)
Whoa, nobody caught me.
That was lame.
I don't think
he's moving.
(laughter)
(snoring)
He is a lazy freeloader,
and it's time
for all this
dysfunction to stop.
Can't we, can't we
just do this later?
I mean, you know how
he gets in the morning.
Ned, aren't you tired
of letting people
push you around?
Yes.
Then get in there
and do it.
(sighs)
(snoring continues)
(snorts):
Oh. What?
What is it?
Dewey, hey...
it's the first of the month
and, uh...
I would like your share
of the rent now, please.
Oh, man, you know
I don't have it.
You wake me up
for that?
Come on, man!
Sorry.
Dewey, I mean, you owe me a lot
of money as it is.
Yeah, try $2,200.
Okay, you guys?
The band is about
to hit it big time.
We're going to win
Battle of the Bands,
and when I'm rolling
in the Benjamins,
I will throw you
and your dog a bone.
Good night.
Oh, give it up!
Your band has never
made two cents.
Patty, come on,
I'm on this.
Oh, you're on this?
You're on this?
He's walking all over you.
Mommy, could we please
talk about this later?
Uh, no, we can't talk
about it later
because Ned and I have
to go to work.
We have jobs.
We contribute to society,
all right?
I am an assistant to the mayor
of this city, hello?
Why? Can you get her
out of here, please?
Why? Why her?
And Ned has the most
important job there is.
Temping?
Dewey, a substitute
teacher is not a temp.
He's a baby-sitter.
Oh, yeah? You think
it's so easy?
Well, I'd like
to see you try.
You wouldn't last one day.
Dude, I service society
by rocking, okay?
I'm out there on the front lines
liberating people with my music.
Rocking ain't no
walk in the park, lady.
All right, this is
useless, all right?
You tell him that
if he doesn't come up
with the rent
by the end of the week,
he's out of here.
Dewey, I'm not paying
your share of the rent,
so, I don't know.
I mean, maybe you
should sell one
of your guitars
or something.
What?
Would you tell Picasso
to sell his guitars?
Oh, my God.
He's an idiot.
Dude...
I've been
mooching off you for years,
and it's never been a problem
until she showed up.
Just dump her, man.
Yeah, well, if you don't
come up with some money,
she's going to dump me;
she's fed up.
Really? Because that would be
a good thing.
She's a nightmare.
Come on. I may never have
another girlfriend...
I mean, just come on.
Come up with some money, please.
Please.
Okay. For you.
Not for her, man. For you.
Thank you.
♪ Heal me
(acoustic guitar plays)
♪ I'm heartsick
D minor...
♪ I'm hungry
♪ And A minor, G, on you
Hey!
♪ Heal my heart...
Hey! What's up?
Is that a new song?
Who's this guy?
Dewey...
we're taking the Battle of
the Bands seriously this year.
Good, 'cause I need the money.
Now listen, my feeling is,
if we're going
to win this thing,
we've got to actually
start playing some music.
I agree. You're fired.
And your lyrics-- don't take
this the wrong way--
are lame.
But I've been sitting
on some awesome material, so...
Dewey, did you hear what I said?
We voted.
You're out.
This is Spider;
he's replacing you.
What's up, dawg?
I was going to tell you
last night, Dewey,
but you passed out, man.
Okay, you're going to kick me
out of the band, huh?
You're going to fire me?
Well, this is my band;
I brought us together.
Theo wanted you out, man,
and there's nothing I could do.
Oh, shut up, man.
You voted him out too.
I didn't tell you
what to do.
THEO:
Dewey, listen to me.
You're a good guitar player.
But it's, it's
the 20-minute solos.
It's the stage dives.
We're trying to land
a record deal here, man,
and you're an embarrassment.
Read between the lines, Theo.
Read between
the lines!
Dewey, man, I hope
this doesn't come between us.
Like, I care
about you, man.
You guys, you know what?
You're nuts.
You're all nuts.
You've been focused
so hard on making it,
you forgot about one little
thing-- it's called the music.
And I don't
even care.
You know what? So what.
I don't want to hang out
with a bunch
of wanna-be corporate sellouts.
I'm going to form my own band
and we are going to start
a revolution, okay?
And you're going to be a funny
little footnote on my epic ass.
I feel sorry for you guys.
DEWEY:
Uh-huh. Yes. Mm-hmm.
Yeah, it's a 1968 Gibson SG.
Mint condish.
No.
That's all?
Well, that's a mistake.
No, Hendrix played this guitar.
Hel... Hello?
(phone rings)
Yeah.
WOMAN:
Is this Mr. Schneebly?
Nah, he's not here.
Oh. Could you
take a message for me?
Um, yeah.
Hi. My name is Rosalie Mullins.
I'm the principal here
at Horace Green Prep,
and we are having
a little emergency here.
One of our teachers broke
her leg
on the way to school
this morning,
and all of our subs
are already working.
Pat Wickam at Milton Prep
recommended I give
Mr. Schneebly a call.
Do you know if he's available?
Uh... how long is the gig?
Excuse me?
Uh, how long is the job?
My guess is as much
as a few weeks,
but we do need somebody
to start immediately.
Mm-hmm.
So how much are we talking here?
We pay our substitutes
$650 a week.
Now, do you know when
Mr. Schneebly will be back?
Hold on a sec.
Oh. You know what?
I think
he's just coming in right n...
Ned, phone!
(with affected voice):
Hello, this is Ned Schneebly.
(engine rumbling)
ROSALIE:
Pat faxed me
your resume.
It's very impressive.
Mm-hmm.
We've never been in a
bind like this before,
so thank you so much.
So how's this
going to work?
Are you going
to pay me up front?
I, I don't understand.
It would be really great
if I could get paid now in cash.
Oh. Well.
We don't do that.
Okay, well when you
cut my check,
just make it payable
to Dewey Finn,
for tax reasons.
You can discuss all of that
with Candace
in Administration,
at the end of the day.
Okay, when's
the end of the day?
We commence at 8:15,
and school lets out at 3:00.
Oh. Uh-oh.
You know what? Uh...
Do you think I could cut out
a little early today?
I got some stuff I got to do.
It's cool. I can stay.
Mr. Schneebly...
this is considered the best
elementary school in the state,
and we maintain that reputation
by adhering to a strict
code of conduct--
faculty included.
You know what?
You don't have to worry about me
because I'm a hard-ass,
and if a kid gets out of line,
I got no problem
smacking them in the head.
No. No, no.
We don't use
corporal punishment here.
Okay, so just verbal abuse?
Mr. Schneebly,
if you have any problems
with any of your students,
you just send them to me.
I will do the disciplining.
Check.
Children...
please take
your seats.
Everyone, I'd like
to introduce
Ms. Dunham's substitute.
This is Mr. Schneebly.
Why don't you write
your name on the board.
Yes...
Yes, I will.
You know what?
Why don't you all
just call me "Mr. S."
Mr. S. has never taught
here at Horace Green,
so I want you all to be
on your best behavior.
So the curriculum
is on the desk.
And do you have
any questions?
Yeah, when's lunch?
The children
just had their lunch.
Is there anything else you need?
Uh...
I'm a teacher.
All I need are minds
for molding.
All right, then.
Well, thanks again;
you saved the day.
Okay, who's got food in here?
You're not going to get
in trouble.
I'm hungry.
You.
What do you got?
Mm-hmm.
That's what I'm
talking about.
(muffled): Okay.
Teach. Teach.
Teach. All right, look,
here's the deal.
I've got a hangover.
Who knows what that means?
Doesn't that mean
you're drunk?
No. It means I was drunk
yesterday.
It means you're
an alcoholic.
Wrong.
You wouldn't come
to work hungover
unless you were
an alcoholic.
Dude, you got a disease.
Hmm. Hmm.
What's your name?
Freddy Jones.
Hmm. Freddy Jones, shut up.
(laughter)
(quietly):
Shut up.
The point is,
you all can just chill today.
We'll start on this crap-ola
tomorrow.
Yes, Tinkerbell?
Summer.
As class factotum,
first, I'd like to just say
welcome to Horace Green.
Thank you.
Do you have any questions
about our schedule?
'Cause usually now
Ms. Dunham teaches vocabulary,
then gives us a pop quiz,
then she'll split us
up into our reading groups.
Track B is...
Okay, hey, hey, hey.
Miss Dumbum ain't your teacher
today, I am,
and I got a headache
and the runs,
so I say-- time for recess.
But Mr. S., that poster
charts everyone's performance.
We get gold stars when we
master the material
covered in class.
How do we get gold stars
if we just have recess?
What are these black dots here?
Demerits.
What kind of a sick school
is this?
Hmm?
(gasping)
Yeah?
As long as I'm here,
there will be no grades
or gold stars or demerits.
We're going to have recess
all the time.
Whoo!
But, Ms. Dunham
only gives us recess
for 15 minutes.
Hey! You're not hearing me,
girl. I'm in charge now.
Okay?
And I say recess.
Go.
Play and have fun now.
Nice.
Now you don't want me
to have to call your
parents, do you?
It's all right, Emily,
don't cry.
Just try to be
a bit more conscientious.
Would you like a hug?
(screams)
I'll be good, I swear!
All right,
well, that's fine, Emily.
You're excused.
Yes, we did it.
We did it, come on.
Give me some.
Give me some of that.
Yeah! Woo-hoo!
I will see you cats
on the flip flop.
Later!
I heard she slipped
in the bathroom?
MULLINS:
Yes, yes, but we've
got, of course,
a wonderful new
substitute
who comes very
highly recommended.
(Dewey hooting)
Mr. Schneebly?
Yeah!
Whoo!
Hold on, buddy!
Oh, my God.
You've got to be kidding me.
Oh, man,
this guy sucks,man.
You've gotta call him.
Call him? Yeah right.
Okay.
Yes, you can be in my band.
But, Ned...
no power plays, man.
I've got vision up the butt,
so just go with it.
No thanks.
You're not
a teacher, Ned.
You're the cross-dressing,
blood-sucking incubus
from Maggot Death.
That's the real you.
Dewey, I'm not
a satanic sex-god anymore.
I'm a working stiff
and that's cool.
She's got you brainwashed, man.
Can you see that I'm working?
That's terrific.
But who are you, babe?
This is my apartment, babe.
Oh... Not if you don't pay
your rent, it's not.
Get a job.
I got a job, okay?
I am going to have your rent
by the end of the week.
Go tell the mayor.
You got a job. Doing what?
I do what Ned does; I'm temping.
I'm not a temp. I'm a sub.
And soon I'll be
a certified teacher.
Come on, man, one show,
$20,000 prize--
we split it 60/40.
Grab your bass and come back
to the garage, brother.
I mean, don't you miss
rocking out?
Dewey, if you think anyone
in their right mind
is going to want to be
in a band with you,
you're more delusional
than I thought.
Dewey, you know,
maybe it's time
to give up those dreams.
I did, and things are going
really great for me.
Are you going to
teach us anything
or are we just
going to sit here?
Just do whatever you want.
(sighs)
I want to learn from my teacher.
Besides that.
Freddy,
what do you
like to do?
I don't know, burn stuff?
Just go out and have recess.
My parents don't spend $15,000
a year for recess.
What, you want
to learn something?
Yes, I do.
What, you want me
to teach you something?
You want to learn
something? All right,
here's a useful lesson for you.
Give up. Just quit.
Because in this life,
you can't win.
Yeah, you can try.
But in the end, you're just
going to lose, big time,
because the world is run
by the man.
Who?
The man?
Oh, you don't know the man?
Well, he's everywhere.
In the White House,
down the hall--
Miss Mullins, she's the man.
And the man ruined the ozone,
and he's burning down
the Amazon,
and he kidnapped Shamu
and put her
in a chlorine tank, okay?
And there used to be
a way to stick it to the man.
It was called Rock and Roll.
But guess what? Oh, no.
The man ruined that too
with a little thing called MTV!
So don't waste your time
trying to make anything cool
or pure or awesome,
'cause the man's
just going to call you
a fat, washed-up loser
and crush your soul.
So do yourselves a favor
and just give up!
Oh.
Mr. Schneebly,
it's after 10:00.
On Tuesdays,
the children have
music class now.
DEWEY:
Right. Okay.
Uh... good work, people.
We will continue
with our lecture on the man
when we return.
Have a good music class.
(faint classical music plays)
(classical music continues)
("Sunshine of Your Love"
by Cream plays)
Mr. S., what's going on?
(strums guitar)
I heard you in music class.
You guys can really play.
Why didn't anyone tell me?
You-- what's
your name?
Zack.
You play the guitar?
Yeah.
Okay, come here.
You ever play the
electric guitar?
My dad won't let me.
He thinks it's
a waste of time.
A waste of...?
Try this one.
Okay, here's a guitar pick.
You pluck along with me,
okay, if you can.
(plays riff from "Iron Man"
by Black Sabbath)
(repeats riff note for note)
(plays riff from "Smoke
on the Water" by Deep Purple)
(repeats riff note for note)
Yes.
(plays riff from
"Highway to Hell" by AC/DC)
(repeats riff)
Yes!
Okay, you stay
right there. Don't move.
Piano man?
Front and center.
Okay.
What's your name?
Lawrence.
Lawrence, you ever
played keyboards?
Any techno?
No, I only play piano.
Okay. All right,
fair enough.
Try this out for me, okay?
Just give this a try
on my count, all right?
One... two...
three... four...
(plays intro to "Touch Me"
by the Doors)
Yes.
♪ Come on, come on
come on, come on ♪
♪ Now touch me, babe
♪ Can't you see
That I am not afraid... ♪
♪ Shaka-kaka
♪ Lawrence is good at piano
♪ He shall be rocking
In my show ♪
(scatting)
Stop. That's perfect.
You're perfect.
Stay right there.
Okay?
You.
Could you come up here please?
What was your name?
Katie.
Katie. What was
that thing
you were playing today,
the big thing?
Cello.
Okay, this is
a bass guitar,
and it's the exact
same thing,
but instead of
playing like this,
you tip it on the side,
chello,you've got a bass.
Try it on.
Okay, now play this note
right here, that's a G.
Okay.
But let your fingers
do the rocking.
Keep that G coming
all day long.
G, G, G, G, G, G...
Good. Stop.
Are there any drummers
in the house?
I play percussion.
That's because you
couldn't play anything else.
Shut up.
Come here, dude.
Just see if you can do
what I do, okay?
Just give it a try.
Okay? Give that a try.
Okay!
That's really good.
Just stay right here.
All right, okay.
Lawrence, give me a G note.
With the fifth above it,
and the middle one.
No middle one,
I changed my mind.
Now go an octave below.
Now give me some rhythm.
Buh, buh, buh...
And keep that same
rhythm-- go.
Okay, Katie, remember that note
I taught you, the G?
Play it, but also keep it
rocking, good.
Bum, bum...
Okay, give me like a...
like a chung chigga, chung
chigga, chung chigga,
chung chigga, chung
chigga, chung chigga...
Good. Okay, no, that's bad.
That's like George
of the Jungle.
Play it up here on the
cymbal but really light.
Chung chigga,
chung chigga...
Oh, that's it! Okay, keep going
with that, Zack.
You remember this thing
I taught you a minute ago?
It goes like...
(plays riff from
"Smoke on the Water")
(playing riff)
Yes. Yes.
Whoa!
All right, let's go!
(playing wild solo)
(yells)
Oh!
All right, stop. Stop.
You guys.
Hey, you guys,
stop messing around.
We've got a lot of work to do.
Okay, people, pay attention
because I do not want
to have to fail you.
I thought you didn't
believe in grades.
Of course I believe in grades.
I was testing you
and you passed.
Good work, Summer.
Four-and-a-half
gold stars for you.
Now, listen, you guys,
you know what?
Normal kids would have
been stoked to slack off,
but not you guys,
'cause you're not normal.
You're special.
And because I think you guys
have the right attitude,
I think it's time we started
our new class project.
A science project?
No.
It's called... Rock Band.
Is this a school project?
Yes.
And it's a requirement.
And it may sound easy...
but nothing could be harder.
It will test your head
and your mind
and your brain, too.
Will other schools be competing?
You could say that.
You could say
that every school in the state
will be competing
for the top prize.
What's the prize?
A win will go
on your permanent record.
Hello, Harvard, yo?
The thing is, we're not
supposed to get started
until next quarter,
but I think we should
get a leg up on the competition,
don't you?
I do.
Who else wants to go
for the gold?
I do.
Yeah.
All right.
But if anyone finds out
what we're doing in here,
we'll be disqualified.
So let's just keep it
on the down-low, shall we?
Can we tell our parents?
No! Just trust me.
They don't want to know
anything about this.
Keep it zipped.
All right, you guys,
let's kick it into overdrive.
What are the rest of us
supposed to do?
You just sit back
and enjoy the magic of rock.
You mean, we're not in the band?
Now, hold up now.
Just 'cause
you're not in the band
doesn't mean
you're not in the band.
We need backup singers.
Who can sing?
You, sing.
♪ The sun'll come out
Yes.
♪ Tomorrow
♪ Bet your bottom dollar
that tomorrow... ♪
Stop.
You've got it,
and I don't even know
what it is, but you've got it.
And that's why
you're in the band.
You, sing.
♪ Amazing Grace
♪ How sweet the sound
♪ That saved...
Stop, before I start crying
because I found
the missing ingredient.
You're in the band.
I can sing.
You can?
Mm-hmm.
All right, Summer, belt it.
(off-key):
♪ Memory
♪ All alone
in the moonlight... ♪
Stop. Stop. Okay.
Good. That's pretty good.
All right.
(kids snickering)
I can also play clarinet,
you know.
I'll find
something for you.
When we get back from lunch,
I'll assign the rest of you
killer positions.
Thank you.
WOMAN:
You're welcome.
There you go.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Mr. Schneebly?
Yeah?
Hey, what's up?
I don't think I
should be in the band.
Why not?
I'm not cool enough.
People in bands are cool.
I'm not cool.
Dude, you are cool.
The way you play.
Wh... why do you say
you're not cool?
Nobody ever talks to me.
Well,
those days are over, buddy,
'cause you could be the ugliest
sad sack on the planet,
but if you're in a rocking band,
you're the cat's pajamas, man,
you're the bee's knees.
Bee's knees?
Yeah, the bee's knees.
You're going to be the most
popular guy in school. Trust me.
Okay. I'll do it.
Now, listen,
this is a big commitment now.
You don't just say yes if you're
going to flake out later.
I won't.
Larry?
Welcome to my world.
Boom.
Okay.
Boom, a couple of these.
Now, here.
Okay.
Now give me a platform.
Let's rock, let's rock today.
Now do it to me.
Let's rock,
let's rock today.
That's good.
Slap it.
Shoot it. Kaboot it.
We're going to work on that
some more later.
It's a very long shake.
Get going.
Good knuckle crack.
("Back in Black"
by AC/DC plays)
Lead guitar...
Zack Attack.
Take a seat.
On bass, Posh Spice.
On keyboards, Mr. Cool.
And on drums, Spazzy McGee.
Okay, Blondie,
Brace Face,
you're singing backup.
All right, Tough Guy,
Shortstop...
Fancy Pants,
get over here.
You guys are on
security detail.
You're job is to make sure
no one outside this room
knows what we're
doing in here.
The future of the
band depends on you.
Okay, your first mission:
soundproofing this room.
Get on it.
Can I be
the band's stylist instead?
Of course you can, Fancy Pants.
Okay.
Carrot Top, Roadrunner,
Turkey Sub,
we are going to have
a lot of equipment.
We're talking amps,
electric guitars,
maybe even lasers
and smoke machines.
Now, your job is to master
the transportation
and operation of
this technology.
Seriously, without
a first-rate roadie crew,
we'll never have
a psychedelic show,
and I can't live with that,
okay?
I'm counting on you.
Get going. Go.
All right.
You three...
groupies, and your
job is simple:
just worship the band.
And you're going
to be making hats;
you're going to
be making T-shirts--
all kind of merchandise.
Which leads me
to your first assignment:
naming the band.
Yes.
All right.
Sit down.
As for me, I will be singing
lead vocal and shredding guitar.
Wait. Isn't this
a student project?
What's your point?
Are you supposed to be
in the band?
What, you want
to get rid of me?
Why, because I'm old?
You hate teachers, is
that what you're about?
No.
Okay, well, teachers
like to play, too.
And not only am I going to play,
I'm El Capitano,
and what I say goes,
so put your hands
over your hearts.
I pledge allegiance
ALL:
to the band
of Mr. Schneebly,
ALL:
and will not fight him
for creative control,
ALL:
and will defer to him
on all issues
related to the musical
direction of the band.
ALL:
And will defer to him
on all issues...
(all mumbling)
Let's get rocking!
ALL:
Yeah!
♪ Substitute
♪ Your lies for fact
♪ I see right through
Your plastic mac ♪
♪ I look all white
But my dad... ♪
(sets parking brake)
Morning, Summer.
Groupie?
What's the matter?
You want me
to be a groupie?
Well, groupie
is an important job.
I researched groupies
on the Internet.
They're sluts;
they sleep with the band.
No. That's not true.
They're like cheerleaders.
I don't want
to be a cheerleader.
Look, my mother is a room parent
and she's not going to be happy
when she hears about this.
Okay, listen.
I didn't want to say this
in front of the other kids
'cause I didn't want
to make them jealous,
but I made a special
position just for you.
And it's the most
important job of all:
band manager.
Band manager?
Oh, yeah.
What's that?
Well, I'm going to
be busy rocking out,
so it's up to you
to make sure
everyone is doing their job.
Summer... you're
in charge of everything.
Okay.
All right. Look alive!
Listen up.
(claps hands)
First thing you do,
when you start a band...
Um, Mr. Schneebly,
before we start,
shouldn't I first
take attendance?
Okay, fine.
Okay.
Now...
Michelle?
Here.
Okay.
And Marco.
Here.
Okay.
Uh, Summer. Here.
Uh, let's see. Tomika?
Okay, we're
all here.
Look, the first thing you do
when you start a band
is talk about your influences.
That's how you figure out
what kind of band
you want to be.
So, who do you like?
Blondie?
Christina Aguilera.
Who? No. Come on. What?
You, Shortstop.
Puff Daddy.
Wrong. Billy?
Liza Minelli?
What are you...?
You guys!
This project
is called "Rock Band."
I'm talking about bands
that rock.
Led Zeppelin.
Don't tell me you guys have
never gotten the Led out.
Jimmy Page? Robert Plant?
Ring any bells?
What about Sabbath?
AC/DC?
Motorhead?
Oh, what do they teach
in this place?!
(sighing):
Summer...
you're the class whatever,
go to the board.
"Factotum."
Factotor.
New schedule.
8:15 to 10:00, Rock History.
10:00 to 11:00,
Rock Appreciation and Theory.
And then band practice until
the end of the day.
What about math?
No. Not important.
World cultures?
Not important.
You guys, we need to focus here.
Don't you want
to win this contest?
It's prestigious.
Um, question.
How are we being graded
in all this?
I mean, since I'm band manager
and I have the most
responsibility, wouldn't...?
Summer, if you grade-grub
one more time,
I will send you back
to the first grade, you got it?
Back to your seat now.
Fine.
What are we going to play?
Uh, you don't have to worry
about that.
We have awesome material,
which I wrote.
Let's hear it.
What?
Let's hear your song.
You want to hear my song?
I'll play you my song,
if you want to hear it.
The thing is,
I just want you to keep in mind,
I wrote it in, like, 15 minutes
and, uh, it's not done yet, and
you might not like it...
Just play the song, Schneebly.
Okay, I will sing it for you,
but, uh, let me just
get in the zone.
I was not planning
on unveiling it,
but I will sing it.
(humming, fluttering lips)
Tip of the tongue,
teeth and the lips.
(hums, flutters lips)
(electronic tone plays)
(hums tone)
Okay.
It starts off...
a dark stage
and then a beam of light
and you can see me
and my guitar.
(imitates electric guitar)
♪ In the end of time
♪ There was a man
Who knew the road ♪
♪ And the writing
Was written on the stone... ♪
And then a thin layer of fog
comes in around my ankles.
Roadies, that means dry ice.
We gonna talk about this later.
♪ In the ancient time
♪ An artist led the way
♪ But no one
seemed to understand ♪
Chimes, Freddy.
♪ In his heart he knew
♪ The artist must be true
♪ But the legend of the rent
was way past due... ♪
Then, Katie, you come in
with the bass.
(scats the bass line)
♪ Well, you think
You'll be just fine ♪
♪ Without me, but you're mine
♪ You think you can
Kick me out of the band... ♪
And then, Zack, you come in
with a face-melter.
(scats electric guitar)
Okay?
♪ Well, there's just
One problem there ♪
♪ The band is mine!
♪ How can you kick me out
Of what is mine? ♪
And then, shh...Hawaii Five-O.
You ever see that show?
Okay, well, there's
a drum solo in it that goes...
Shiga jigga,
jigga, jigga, jigga.
♪ You're not hardcore
Unless you live hardcore ♪
And then, that's where I want
the backup singers to be, like,
♪ Well, you're not hardcore
(falsetto):
♪ No, you're not hardcore...
♪ Unless you live hard...
(falsetto):
♪ Unless you live hardcore
♪ But the legend of the rent
Was way hardcore... ♪
Boom! Big ol' explosion.
Some, like, confetti comes down.
Anyway, that's all I got so
far-- It's a work in progress.
I liked it, Mr. Schneebly.
I thought it was really catchy.
Thank you.
Mr. S.? Mm-hmm.
We came up with some
names for the band.
Yeah? Hit me.
The Bumblebees?
Uh... No, it's sissy.
The Koala Bears?
No. What are you talking about?
It's too sissy.
Okay, girls, I need to speak
with Principal Mullins.
Hey, Miss Mullins. Hello.
How's it going?
How about Pig Rectum?
Sh...
Michelle!
It's a science
project. Never mind.
Listen, Ros, I was thinking
about organizing a field trip
for the kids at the
end of the month.
What do you think
about that?
Well, um... substitutes,
as a rule, do not
organize field trips.
Right, but I figure
I'm going to be here
for a while so...
Well, that
remains to be seen.
Have you met
some of our other teachers?
No, but listen,
don't you think
the kids could learn
by getting out
of the classroom?
You know, it's more complicated
than that, all right?
There's safety issues.
Parents need
to be notified, all right?
It's against
school policy.
Mr. S.,
I have a lot of ideas.
Hmm?
How about, everyone
in magenta
with beads
and sequins?
Billy, Billy,
can't you see
I'm talking
to Principal Mullins?
Oh, hi.
William?
I'll make up some samples.
Everyone?
This is Ned Schneebly.
He's covering for Gail.
This is Gabe Green.
He teaches second.
Hello.
Jane Lemmons, fourth.
Hey, there.
Bob's our PE teacher
and Roberta is
our librarian.
How do you do?
Would you care
to join us, Mr. Schneebly?
Yeah.
Did I say that correctly?
Schneebly?
Actually,
it's "Schnayblay."
We were just
discussing testing.
Mm-hmm.
Which test do you
find most effective?
The TASS or the
Wilson-Binet?
DEWEY:
Mmm. I-I say no testing,
and I will
tell you why, Joe.
Gabe.
I believe that the children
are the future.
Now, listen, you
can teach them well,
but, buddy, you have got
to let them lead the way.
Let the children's
laughter just remind us
how we used to be.
That's what I decided,
long ago.
Isn't that a song?
Hmm? No.
No... Uh, I don't think so. No.
No?
No, it isn't.
Mm-mm.
♪ So you think
You'll be just fine ♪
♪ Without me, but you're mine
♪ You think you can
Kick me out of the band? ♪
♪ Well, there's
Just one problem there ♪
♪ The band is mine
♪ How can you kick me out
of what is mine? ♪
Everybody...
♪ 'Cause you're not hardcore
♪ No, you're not hardcore
♪ Unless you live hardcore
♪ And the legend of the rent was
Way hardcore ♪
All right.
Good. Stop.
Okay, Freddy, that was awesome.
You're rocking, but it's
a little sloppy Joe.
Tighten up the
screws, okay?
Zack, dude, what's up
with the stiffness man?
You're looking...
a little robotronic. Okay?
Let's, uh, grease up the hinges,
and listen--
loosey-goosey, baby,
loosey-goosey.
I'm just playing it
the way you told me.
I know, and you know
what? It's perfect.
But the thing is, rock is
about the passion, man.
Where's the joy?
You're the lead guitarist
and we are counting on you
for some style, brotha.
So try this out.
This is an ancient technique.
It's called "power stance."
That's it. Power stance.
You own the universe.
Now give me an E chord.
Just go... Ugh!
But let me hear, "Ugh!"
Ugh!
Yeah, now raise
your goblet of rock.
It's a toast to
those who rock.
Now smile and
nod your head
and let me see
your eyeballs wide
like there's something
wrong. Yeah! Yeah.
Do it again. Give me that...
That's what I'm
talking about.
Okay, let's do it again
from "You're
not hardcore."
One, two, three...
♪ Well, you're not hardcore
♪ Unless you live hardcore
♪ And the legend of the rent
Was way hardcore ♪
Yeah! Now we're rocking.
Your homework is to listen
to some real music.
Get inspired.
For Blondie, Blondie.
For Lawrence, Yes.
That's the name
of the band.
Listen to the keyboard
solo on "Roundabout."
It will blow the classical
music out your butt.
Okay, for you, Rush.
2112. Neil Peart.
One of the great
drummers of all time.
Study up.
Um, are we going
to be goofing off
like this every day?
Uh, we're not goofing off.
We're creating
musical fusion.
Well, um, are we going
to be creating
musical fusion every day?
Yeah. Get used to it.
Okay, and for you,
Jimi Hendrix.
Axis Bold As Love.
Dude, are you psyched
about the new project?
Sure.
"Sure"? Hey.
Wait a minute. What's up, man?
Are you the...?
You're the lead guitarist
of an unbelievable rock band.
This is a dream
come true for you.
Okay.
All right.
I'll see you.
Mr. S.?
Hey, Tomika, what's up?
I don't want
to be a roadie.
What? Why not?
It's an important job.
All right. Well...
You want to be,
uh... Security?
I want to be a singer.
A singer?
Okay. Sing
me something.
Tomica, I can't let you
be a singer
if you can't sing.
♪ You told me
To leave you alone ♪
♪ My papa said
"Come on home" ♪
♪ My doctor said
"Take it easy" ♪
♪ But your lovin'
Is much too strong ♪
♪ I'm welded to your
Chain, chain, chain... ♪
Oh, my goodness.
Nice pipes, Tomika.
Why didn't you
raise your hand
when I was looking for singers?
You're in.
Welcome aboard.
Oh, okay. Perfect.
Pink Floyd, Dark
Side of the Moon.
Listen to the vocal solo
on "The Great
Gig in the Sky."
All right?
All right.
♪ One, two, three,
four, five, six! ♪
♪ Roadrunner, roadrunner
♪ Going faster miles an hour
Off to work. Bye-bye.
♪ With the radio on
♪ And I say "roadrunner"
Once, "roadrunner" twice ♪
♪ I'm in love
With rock 'n' roll ♪
♪ And I'll be out all night
You can play your music after
you finish your homework,
after you finish your chores,
but not until then.
Zack! Zack,
do not walk away from me
when I'm talking to you.
It's very rude.
All right? Last thing.
You do your guitar
after your homework and chores
and only what Miss Schoncott
gives you, all right?
No more
rock music. Okay?
ZACK: Okay.
FATHER: All right, get to class.
Watch that attitude.
Do you have
another blanket?
(indistinct chatter)
That's good.
(claps hands)
All right.
Everybody, class has begun.
And you know what?
You guys have been doing
real good in here,
and if I was going to give you
a grade,
I would give you an "A,"
but that's the problem.
Rock ain't about
doing things perfect.
Who can tell me
what it's really about?
Frankie?
Uh... Scoring chicks?
N-no.
See. No.
Eleni?
Getting wasted.
N... Come on. No.
Leonard.
Sticking it to the man?
Yes! But you can't
just say it, man.
You got to feel it
in your blood and guts.
If you want to rock,
you gotta break the rules.
You gotta get mad at the man,
and right now I'm the man.
That's right, I'm the man,
and who's got
the guts to tell me off? Huh?
Who's going to tell me off?
Shut the hell up, Schneebly!
That's it, Freddy.
That's it.
Who can top him?
Get out of here, stupid ass.
DEWEY:
Yes, Alicia.
You're a joke.
You're the worst
teacher I've ever had.
Summer. That is great.
I like the delivery
because I felt your anger.
Thank you.
You're a fat loser
and you have body odor.
All right. All right.
Now is everyone nice
and pissed off?
ALL: Yeah!
Good.
Time to write a rock song.
Now, what makes you mad more
than anything in the world?
Billy?
You.
Billy, we've already
told me off.
Let's move on.
You're tacky
and I hate you.
Okay, you see me after class.
You. Gordon.
No allowance.
♪ I didn't get
No allowance today ♪
♪ So now I'm really
Ticked off ♪
You know what I mean?
What else makes you mad?
Michelle?
Chores.
♪ I had to do my chores today
♪ So I am really ticked off
What else?
Bullies.
♪ All you bullies
Get out of my way ♪
♪ 'Cause I am
Really ticked off ♪
So what would you say
to a bully? Zack?
I don't know.
Now, come on.
If someone was right
up in your grill,
what would you say?
I don't know.
If someone was
pushing you around,
telling you what to do,
what would you say?
Step off?
♪ Step off!
♪ Step off! Step off!
Everybody!
♪ Step off!
♪ If I do what you say
♪ I might turn into a robot
♪ Do my chore day after day
♪ And they don't want any lip
♪ No! So step off! Step off!
♪ Step off!
Step off! Step off! ♪
Am I right?
♪ Step off! Step off!
(snarls)
(kids laughing)
(snarling)
All right, now that was
a perfectly decent rock song.
(laughter)
Grazie. Grazie.
Oh, yeah.
I was this close
to getting a chair
on the Polish Philharmonic,
and I nailed the audish,
but I didn't get it.
Guess who did.
Yo-Yo Ma's cousin.
Little nepotis.
But, anyway, I just decided
to give up on myself
and become a teacher,
because those that can't do,
teach.
And those that can't teach,
teach gym. Am I...?
(all laughing)
Aw, I'm just...
I'm just joshing.
Cute.
Hey, Mr. Schneebly.
Hey, Zack.
Just wanted to say,
that was a really
cool lesson today.
Well, thanks, dude.
I'll see you back in class.
Okay.
(rock music playing)
♪ You've got
To pick up the pieces ♪
♪ C'mon, sort your trash
♪ You better pull yourself
Back together ♪
♪ Maybe you've got
Too much cash ♪
♪ Better call, call the law
♪ When you gonna
Turn yourself in? ♪
♪ Yeah, you're a politician
♪ Don't become one
Of Hitler's children ♪
♪ Bonzo goes to Bitburg
♪ Then goes out
For a cup of tea ♪
♪ As I watched it on TV,
Somehow it really bothered me ♪
♪ Drank in all the bars in town
For an extended foreign policy ♪
♪ Pick up the pieces
♪ Bah... bah-bah-bah
♪ My brain
Is hanging upside down ♪
♪ Bah... bah-bah-bah
♪ I need something
To slow me down ♪
♪ Bah... bah-bah-bah
♪ Ooh, yeah
♪ My brain is hanging
Upside down ♪
♪ Bah... bah-bah-bah
♪ And I need something
To slow me down ♪
(musical break)
♪ Shouldn't wish you happiness
♪ Wish her the very best
♪ $50,000 dress
♪ Shaking hands
with Your Highness ♪
♪ See through you
Like cellophane ♪
♪ You watch the world complain
♪ But you do it anyway
♪ Who am I... am I to say?
♪ Bonzo goes to Bitburg
♪ Then goes out
For a cup of tea ♪
♪ As I watched it on TV
Somehow it really bothered me ♪
♪ Drank in all the bars in town
For an extended foreign policy ♪
♪ Pick up the pieces
♪ My brain is hanging
Upside down... ♪
I'm just saying,
name two great chick drummers.
Sheila E?
Meg White from
the White Stripes?
She can't drum.
She's a better
drummer than you.
At least she has rhythm.
Freddy, where
are your sleeves?
And what have you
done to your hair?
It's called punk.
Well, it's
not school uniform.
Miss Mullins, you're the man.
Thank you, Frankie.
(snickering)
Good morning, everyone.
Just a reminder:
Parents' Night is coming up,
and I do expect everyone
to have a presentation.
What? Oh! Oh!
MAN: You okay?
Sorry.
As you know, it is the most
important event of the year.
The parents will be
scrutinizing our every move,
so I find it's best
to over-prepare. Right?
The best defense
is a good offense.
And, um... Roberta,
now that I see you...
Hey, is, uh...
Is she always like that?
(chuckles)
Oh, yeah.
Except for the time she got
drunk at the Alumni Dinner.
Oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh...
You should
have seen that.
She got up on the table
and did a Stevie Nicks
impersonation.
And she wasn't bad.
Remember, she took
up the tablecloth
and whirled
around with it?
...that had been
on the turkey tray,
that touched over onto the
peanut butter and jelly tray.
Now, I... I know that you know
that this is a severe problem.
(heavy metal music plays)
Clear.
Go, go, go!
All right, you guys,
is everybody ready?
Yeah.
Strap in.
Let's do this.
Oh, dude, cool.
Three worms.
That's very clever.
DEWEY:
In 1492, Columbus
sailed the ocean...?
Blue.
DEWEY:
Blue. That's right. Okay.
Now, Columbus had three boats--
the Nina, the...?
Gordon?
The Pinta.
Pinta. That's right. And...?
Marco?
Santa Marina?
The Santa Marina. That's good.
Actually, it's the Santa Maria.
Okay. Now you got...
Listen. Pay attention, kids.
I'm not afraid to flunk every...
She's gone.
What's up, dude?
Whoa! Check out
these little kids, man.
Hey, shut up.
Oh, Sorry.
Thought this was the
Battle of The Bands,
not the, uh...
Mickey Mouse Club.
Hey, you want a piece of me?
Hey, look at this guy.
Freddy? Freddy!
Come on, man.
We've got to focus up,
you guys.
We got to nail
this audition.
Mr. S?
What's up?
I don't think
I can sing.
What are
you talking about?
Come here.
So, Tomika,
what's going on?
What do you mean,
you can't sing?
I don't feel good.
I feel sick.
Just let Alicia
and Marta do it.
No. They can't sing like you
can. I need you in the chorus.
What is it? Are you nervous?
Yeah? Why?
What are you afraid of?
They're gonna laugh at me.
What? Why would
they laugh at you?
I don't know. 'Cause I'm fat?
Tomika... (sighs)
Hey, you've got something
everybody wants.
You've got talent, girl.
You have an incredible
singing voice,
and I'm not
just saying that.
You heard of Aretha Franklin,
right?
Okay, she's
a big lady.
But when she starts singing,
she blows people's minds.
Everybody wants to party
with Aretha!
And, uh...
you know
who else has a weight issue?
Who?
Me. But once I get up onstage,
start doing my thing,
people worship me.
Because I'm sexy...
and chubby, man.
Why aren't you on a diet?
Because I like to eat.
Is that such a crime?
Look, you know what?
That's not even the point.
The thing is,
you're a rock star now.
All you got to do is you
just got to go out there,
just rock your heart out.
People are going to dig you, I swear.
Let's just go out there,
show them what you got.
What do you say?
Okay.
Thank you.
Let's rock.
Okay. We are good to go.
No, we're not. Freddy took off.
What? Where?
Some guys invited him
out to their van.
What?! Come on, you guys!
Freddy? Hey, have you seen
a little kid, like, yea high?
Huh? Dang it.
Freddy,
this is your teacher talking!
Hey, Mr. S.
Oh, man!
What's going on here?
Nothing.
Just chilling.
Freddy Jones, you get out
of that van this instant.
See you guys.
Hey, man, you think
you're pretty funny,
partying with
an innocent little kid?
Dude, we're...
we're just chilling.
That kid's
ten years old, man.
He looks up to you, and you
are setting an example for him,
so quit messing around,
and start acting
like a responsible adult!
That goes for all of you guys.
Don't make me come back here.
Come on. Let's go.
What's the big deal?
You're acting
like my mom.
What's the big deal?
You had me
worried sick, man.
I was just hanging out
with some real rockers.
You listen to me.
Those aren't real rockers;
they're posers.
Rock ain't about getting loaded
and acting like a jerk.
Now, this is serious
business here, man.
We got a mission.
Putting on a great show
is the most important
thing you can do.
One great rock show
can change the world.
Do you understand me?
Yeah.
And if you ever scare me
like that again,
so help me, I will...
I will send a note home
to your parents. Let's go.
All right, you guys,
just wait here for a minute.
Hey, man,
look at this stage.
Yeah. It's cool.
DEWEY:
Hey, what's going on?
Where is everyone?
Uh... auditions are over.
What? Who's in charge?
Listen,
you can't leave.
You haven't
heard our band.
Sorry. The bill is full.
We're already overbooked.
No, no, no. Let us just play one
song. We're all here.
We're ready to go.
Who are they?
They're my band.
Kids? What is this?
Some kind of gimmick?
No, it's not a gimmick.
I know they're kids, but they're
awesome. Just listen.
Look, thanks
for coming down,
but you're really not
what we're looking for.
You listen to me!
These kids
have worked their
little fingers to the bone
just to play one song for you,
so you just sit down,
shut up, and listen!
Sheila... call Security.
(sighing):
Oh, God.
SUMMER:
Look, it was
just a warm-up gig.
We'll still
be able to compete
against the other schools
next quarter.
What are
you talking about?
This is the gig, Summer.
This was our Woodstock.
Then we shouldn't
take no for an answer.
What...? Don't take no
for an answer?
He was...? Did you see?
He was going to call the fuzz.
Would you just listen to me?
I have an idea.
Hi, there. Hi.
It's okay. It's cool.
I just wanted to say
I'm really sorry.
I shouldn't have
barged in here
without telling you
what was going down.
It wasn't fair to you,
and it wasn't fair to the kids,
especially after everything
they've been through.
And I... God!
I feel like a jerk.
God! I just... I'm taking them
back to the hospital.
Just wanted to
say I'm really sorry.
That's okay. That's fine.
See, I volunteer
down at Saint Margarita's
in the children's wing,
teaching music.
Really?
Th-th-that's nice.
That's very nice.
Actually, no, it isn't,
because
I totally screwed up.
I told the kids
if they practice,
they'd get into
Battle of the Bands.
What did you
tell them that for?
I don't know.
I just...
I wanted to give them
something to look forward to,
something to keep
their spirits up.
Oh... look at them.
They're terminal.
Every last one of them.
Geez.
Yeah,
and all they wanted to do
before they bit the dust
was play Battle of the Bands.
What do they all have?
It's a, uh...
(clears throat)
It's a rare blood disease.
Stick-it-to-da-man-i-osis.
What's that?
I've never heard of it.
You're lucky.
Because it's hell.
Wow!
We're on the bill.
(cheering)
Cut it out!
You're dying, remember?
(all coughing)
Get in the van.
("The Immigrant Song"
by Led Zeppelin plays)
(screaming)
♪ We come from the land
Of the ice and snow ♪
♪ From the midnight sun
Where the hot springs blow ♪
♪ The hammer of the gods...
Summer, you get an A-plus
and 50 gold stars.
I didn't do it for the grade.
Give me some of that.
Yeah!
♪ Valhalla, I am coming...
(indistinct chatter)
(strumming guitar)
DEWEY: ♪ Ay-ay... ay-ay
♪ Eeh-ay-ay-ay
♪ Ay-ay, oh-oh
♪ Yeah, huh, huh
Hey, Mr. S.
Hmm-mm.
We have a name
for the band.
Hit me.
The School of Rock.
The School... of Rock.
And we shall teach rock
and roll to the world.
♪ There's no way you can stop
♪ The School of Rock... yeah
Stop.
We have a Red Alert.
It's Mullins.
To your positions.
To your positions!
Come on, come on.
And therefore,
E equals M C-squared.
Oh, Miss Mullins.
Come in.
I'm sorry to interrupt,
but Miss Lemmons
said she heard music
coming
from the classroom.
DEWEY:
Music?
Uh... music.
I haven't heard any music.
Uh-oh, you know what?
Miss Lemmons must be on crack,
right, kids?
KIDS:
Mm-hmm.
Well... well... what's that?
Oh, that. Yeah.
Hmm...
we were singing.
We were singing
and we were learning.
We were learning
in sing-song.
Huh... one of your methods?
Mmm-hmm. Yeah.
I find that it's really helpful
when you're teaching
the subjects
that are the boring subjects...
Huh.
Well, you don't mind
if I just sit in
on your class
this afternoon, do you?
No. No.
Come on back this afternoon.
It is the afternoon.
I meant now.
So, please, just continue
with your method.
Yeah.
Okay.
(strums guitar)
♪ Math is a wonderful thing
♪ Math is a really cool thing
♪ So get off your ath
Let's do some math ♪
♪ Math, math, math, math, math
♪ Three minus four is...
Negative one.
That's right.
♪ And six times a billion
Is... ♪
Six billion?
Nailed it.
♪ And 54 is 45 more than...
What is the answer, Marta?
Nine.
♪ No, it's eight
♪ No, it's nine
♪ Yes, I was testing you
♪ It's nine
♪ And that's a magic number
(excited chatter and laughter)
I'm very happy that you're
able to extend your stay,
but I, I must say I-I find
your methods of teaching
very unusual.
Well, I did study with
Dr. Errol Von Straussenburger...
becken.
Who?
Oh, you don't know him?
Oh, he's... he's like one
of the leading leaders
in... unusual methods.
Actually, he's how
I was appointed to
the Presidential Council
for Experimental
Educationers.
That sounds very impressive,
but we're not interested
in experimental education here.
So, if from now on,
if you could
just stick to the curriculum,
that would be great.
Yes. Right.
Thank you.
Uh, Ros...
Yes?
Do you know I would really love
to talk some more
about your philosophy
on, you know, teaching.
Do you think maybe we
could grab some coffee?
You want to go
get some coffee with me?
Yeah. I really would.
(rock music plays)
And you're sure
you don't have any coffee?
Uh-huh. I'm quite sure.
Well, I-I've never
been here before.
Mmm...
I-I-I've never been to this side
of town
before, in fact.
Mmm... ahh.
So, I, uh, have been...
well, I have been... dying
to ask you something,
Mr. Schneebly.
Please, call me Dewey.
Dewey?
Ned?
Call me "Ned."
I was thinking
of my other name.
My middle name.
Oh.
Yeah.
Well, um, Ned...
in your experience, how
does Horace Green compare
to the other schools
that you've taught at?
Oh...
your school is the best.
You're just saying that.
I'm not.
Do you know that kids
at other schools
just have fun all the time?
They're running around.
There's no discipline.
They're happy.
It's anarchy.
This is the best school
I have ever teached at.
I swear.
I'll drink to that.
(chuckling)
You stay right there.
I'm going to go put on
some music.
Oh.
(playing "Edge of 17"
by Stevie Nicks)
♪ Just like
The white winged dove ♪
♪ Sings a song
Sounds like she's singing ♪
♪ Ooh... ooh... ooh...
I love this song.
Really?
Yes.
Stevie Nicks.
Yeah.
Stevie!
You know, she came to town
and she did a concert
and she was just so...
whacked!
Oh, oh, my gosh.
I know. Oh, man.
She put on the best show
I've ever seen.
(humming)
And she is so much better live
then she is on the album.
You know what I mean.
Yes, yes.
Oh, my gosh,
no comparison.
Yeah. You know what?
Oh, man, I would love
to take the kids to a concert.
Concert?
Yeah. There's one at the end
of the month.
It would be perfect.
The Philharmonic.
They do the classics.
They do Beethoven, Mozart,
Enya...
that kind of stuff.
Huh?
Oh, but you guys have a policy
about field trips, huh?
Would it be educational?
"Would it be educational?"
It could be very educational.
Maybe we can make
an exception.
Yes!
♪ Sing a song
Sounds like she's singing ♪
♪ Ooh, baby
♪ Ooh, ooh...
I'm holding you to that.
Make an exception...
(scatting melody)
♪ Ooh
♪ Baby, ooh, said, ooh
♪ Well, I went today
♪ Maybe I will go again...
♪ Tomorrow...
DEWEY:
♪ Keeping your head
Over water ♪
♪ Making a wave if you can't
♪ Temporary layoff, good time
♪ Easy credit
Rip-off, good time ♪
♪ Scratchin' and
Survivin', good time ♪
Would you stop
that, please?
Yeah.
I had a... I had
a really nice time.
Yeah, ditto.
You know, this
is the first time
any teacher has ever
asked me to do anything
outside of school.
No way.
It's, it's true.
In... six years.
Well, you know,
I think it might just
be one of those things
where people are a
little intimidated.
Intimidated?
They hate me.
No. They don't.
Yes, they do.
They sure do.
I can see.
I wasn't always
like this, you know.
wound this tight.
There was a time
when I was fun.
I was funny.
I was, but you can't be funny
and be the... the principal
of a prep school.
No. You cannot,
because when it comes
to their kids,
these parents...
they have no sense of humor.
No. And, and if,
anything goes wrong,
it's my head. All right?
It's my head
in the smasher.
These parents will come down
on me like a nuclear bomb.
I can't make a mistake.
I gotta be perfect,
and that pressure
has turned me into one thing
that I never wanted to be...
(mouthing words)
No. You're not.
Yes, I am.
I am a big one.
Well, I don't think so.
I think you're
pretty cool.
Really?
No.
Yeah. You're way cool.
Really?
(rock guitar plays)
SUMMER:
Okay, drums?
DEWEY: House.
SUMMER:
Keyboards?
DEWEY: House.
Amps? Mm-hmm.
All right. Cable? Got 'em.
All right. Guitar?
Yes.
Mr. S.
Yeah?
What do you think?
Mmm!
Uh...
I don't know. I...
They might be
a little distracting.
It's glitter rock
and it's glam
and its fabulous.
Billy, it's just
not the right style.
Style? You're gonna to talk
to me about style?
You can't even dress yourself.
Look at that bow tie.
Don't you be talking
about my bow tie.
You know what? I give up.
They can just wear their
uniforms.
That's not a bad idea.
Not a bad idea?
I was kidding.
Excuse me.
(playing chords)
Hey, hey, ho-ha.
What is that?
What's what?
What are you playing?
It's just
something I wrote.
You wrote a song?
Well, let's hear it.
Nah, it's not that good.
Come on, I want to hear it,
Kurt Cobain.
Okay, but I'm not
much of a singer.
That's all right.
♪ Baby, we were making
Straight A's ♪
♪ But we were stuck
In a dumb daze ♪
♪ Don't take much
To memorize your lies ♪
♪ Feel like
I've been hypnotized... ♪
Wait. You wrote that?
You wrote that?
Okay, that's it.
You guys?
Rock and roll positions.
What are you doing?
What am I doing?
We're going to learn your song.
But why?
Because that's what
bands do, man--
play each other's songs.
You got lyrics?
Hook me up.
No more secret songs.
All right, Lawrence,
no more reading.
Time for rock.
Get on the drum.
Bass it up.
What was that first chord?
"D."
Play it.
D...
Mm-hmm.
C...
G...
Mm-hmm.
C...
♪ Baby, we were
Making straight A's ♪
Yeah. Yeah.
♪ But we were stuck
In a dumb daze ♪
Mm-hmm.
♪ Don't take much
To memorize your lies ♪
ALL:
♪ And if you want to be
The teacher's pet ♪
♪ Baby, you just
Better forget it ♪
♪ Rock is the reason
Rock is the rhyme... ♪
You know what would be
better though?
You know what
would be better?
If it was rock got no reason,
rock got no rhyme.
You know? Can we try that?
And also, we need some,
Ooh, la-la's.
So like, Ooh, la-la-la,
ooh, la-la-la.
Try that at the chorus, okay?
Can we try it
from the chorus?
One, two, three, four.
One, two, three...
♪ And if you want
To be the teacher ♪
♪ Ooh, la-la-la, ooh, la-la-la
♪ You just better forget it
♪ Rock got no reason
♪ Ooh, la-la-la, ooh, la-la-la
♪ Get me to school on time
♪ And if you want
To be the teacher ♪
♪ Ooh, la-la-la, ooh, la-la-la
♪ You just better forget it
♪ Rock got no reason
♪ Ooh, la-la-la, ooh, la-la-la
♪ You better get me
To school on time ♪
Wow! Boop!
(scatting guitar solo)
I'm going to take
a solo there
if it's cool with you.
All right.
And then you
can solo later.
Okay.
But let me just rock
a solo there, I can feel it.
(scatting guitar solo)
All right...
tomorrow is the big day,
so get your rest.
No late-night parties,
drinking tequila
and trying to get lucky.
Chances like this do not
come around every day.
Now, you've played hard
in here people,
and I am proud of every
last stinking one of you.
So let's just give this
everything we got.
We may fall on our faces,
but if we do, we will fall
with dignity!
With a guitar in our hands
and rock in our hearts!
And in the words of AC/DC--
"We roll tonight
to the guitar bite
"and for those about to rock...
I salute you."
(kids chatting indistinctly)
Ros, excuse me,
I just wanted to remind you
about our little
field trip tomorrow.
What field trip?
The educational concert
we were talking about.
Oh. Oh, I forgot
about that.
I don't know, you know,
school policy
is very difficult
to get around
in this situation.
But you said...
Remember, you said we could
make an exception,
and the kids are all excited
about hearing some Mozart.
I know,
but... the preparations,
there's not enough time,
I don't know anything
about it. Where is it?
Well, I've got it
all covered. What's going on?
Are you mad at me
or something?
No, no, Ned.
I'm sorry, I'm just
a little stressed out
because it's
Parents' Night tonight.
Hey, it's all gonna be fine.
Ned?
Would you mind coming with me
tonight to Parents' Night?
It wouldn't be a date
or anything like that.
It's just that, you know,
I get nervous around the parents
and there's something about you
that makes me feel
a little more relaxed.
You know what, that sounds
so great, Ros, but, uh...
But what?
I wasn't planning
on going tonight.
But you have to come.
You're their teacher.
You have to give
the presentation.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
No, I got you.
I'm ready for that.
So we'll go together?
Okay. Uh, why don't you
pick me up at say 6:40.
Done. Okay.
All right.
♪ You dance
♪ With your lizard
Leather boots on... ♪
What are you
all dressed up for?
Uh, I got a hot date.
That's weird.
I got a check from
Horace Green Prep for $1,200.
I've never even
worked there.
♪ You're a gutter-gaunt
Gangster... ♪
What are you doing?
Calling the school.
♪ John Lennon...
Hi, this is Ned Schneebly...
♪ And I've seen his. Rock!
Dewey...
what's going on?
I told them 15 times,
make it out to cash!
Dewey?
I did something bad, Ned.
No.
Yeah.
They called looking for a sub
and I said I was you
just to make some money;
but then I got there
and the kids, they rock, man.
There's this kid Larry
who's like, "I'm not cool,"
but now he's all...
(scatting jazzy riff)
And there's this other girl
who can sing like... (humming)
...but then she thought
she was too fat to sing,
so they were all dying
of this rare blood disease,
and the principal
got drunk...
And now we're playing tomorrow
at Battle of the Bands,
isn't that great?
It's the coolest thing
that ever happened.
One day, that's all I ask, Ned,
and then I will come clean.
I'll tell everyone
it was my fault.
He had nothing to do with it;
you'll be fine. One day!
PATTY: Ned, home.
Don't say anything to her.
Please. She'll blow it.
She'll blow it...
Don't say anything. Please.
♪ ...Alan Freed did
♪ There are things in night...
Hey. What's going on?
Nothing.
I got a hot date,
that's what's going on.
See you later.
What's going on, Ned?
Nothing.
Nothing? Well...
(rock beat plays)
♪ I'm an alligator
♪ I'm a Mama-Papa
Comin' for you ♪
♪ I'm a space invader
♪ I'll be a rock 'n' rollin'
Bitch for you ♪
♪ Keep your mouth shut...
Okay, I don't think
I can go in there.
What's wrong? Ros...
I'm not a teacher.
Oh, Ned.
A substitute is a teacher.
No, no.
I'm not a teacher; I'm a fraud.
No. You're not.
You're a dedicated,
talented teacher,
and those parents are gonna
love you.
Now just get in there
and tell those parents
what you've been
teaching their kids.
DEWEY:
Yeah, you know, uh,
math, English,
uh... what, science,
what else?
Uh, geography, history,
Latin, Spanish, French,
Latin, uh, math...
did I say that, right?
Anyway, you know,
just all this stuff
you want your kids to know,
it's being covered, okay?
So...
it was great to meet
you all and, uh, drive safe.
MAN:
Excuse me.
Ever since you started
teaching here,
all my son can talk about
is music.
He says when he grows up,
he wants to be a musician.
Is this your influence?
Yeah, well, Mr. Schneebly,
why has my daughter become
obsessed with David Geffen?
And how is this homework?
Okay, see, I would like
to tell you
about what we've been doing
in here,
but there's such a thing as
teacher-student confidentiality
and I don't want to be in breach
of educational law
because I could be dismembered
by the teacher's union.
So...
You expect us
to believe this garbage?
I...
TOMIKA:
Mr. S., don't you think
you should just tell them
about the project?
What project?
LARRY:
Our class project.
Every school in
the state is competing.
MAN:
Competing?
It's not till next quarter,
but Mr. S. wanted us
to get a head start.
WOMAN:
Well, what's
the project, Summer?
It's prestigious.
It will go on
our permanent record, Mom.
Hmm.
You might as well tell
them, Mr. Schneebly.
Okay, look,
I've gotten to know your kids
over the past few weeks
and they are awesome.
Zack is an insane guitarist.
He's the next Hendrix,
and he's ten years old.
And Gordon here,
he's a genius!
He did a whole
professional light show
on his computer in three days.
And, um,
and-and-and Marta here,
she's-she's...
she can hit an "A"
above high "C."
Did you know that?
Because that's tough.
Not many singers
can do that.
And-and, uh...
uh... uh...
Summer, Summer is going to be
the first woman President
of the United States
of America,
and she could run later
this year even
and I would vote for her.
Look, you guys, they're
just all really cool kids.
If they were mine,
I would be so proud.
And I am proud,
just to even know them.
And, um...
Sir, can I see you in
the hall for a moment?
Can I just... let me just say
a couple more things.
MAN:
What's going on?
What's happening,
Officer?
Apparently, that man
is not Ned Schneebly.
What?
This man is Ned Schneebly.
Yeah, he's not
even a teacher.
You called the cops?
She did. She got it out of me. Sorry.
You're apologizing to him?
Sorry.
Ned.
Ned, is-is this true?
Who are you?
My name is Dewey Finn
and, no, I'm not
a licensed teacher,
but I have been touched
by your kids
and I'm pretty sure
I've touched them.
What?
Oh, my God.
(angry murmuring)
(fast rock beat plays)
I've nothing to say to you.
Me, either. Okay.
I'm going to bed.
You know, Dewey,
it's one thing to
throw your life away,
but then to put Ned's
career in jeopardy
is so selfish.
Hey, you're the one who told me
to be like Ned
and get a job.
Yeah, I told you to
be like Ned, Dewey,
I didn't tell
you to be Ned.
And you're not even
going to apologize?
You're the one
who should apologize
for calling the cops.
It's not like I
murdered anybody,
I just wanted to play
a great show.
I was this close.
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
Would you both just
cut it out for one second?
(sighs)
(door slams)
Look, I'm sorry, dude.
I was desperate.
You can't understand.
It was easy for you
to give up music.
It ain't easy for me.
It wasn't easy for me.
I miss it.
Well, then why'd
you give it up?
Because I couldn't keep
kidding myself anymore.
You can blame it
all on bad luck,
but in the end,
maybe we just weren't that good.
Sometimes you got to know
when to quit.
Maybe you're right,
maybe I suck.
That's not
what I said.
Well, music is my life, man.
What do you want me to do?
I don't know.
But... I think it's time
you moved out.
Sorry.
So his name really wasn't
Mr. Schneebly?
No, it was, like,
Dewey something.
What about the project?
Wake up, Marco,
there was no project.
He just wanted us to play a show
so we could make some money.
I can't believe we weren't
getting graded on any of this.
What are you so
bummed about?
We had a three-week vacation.
Yeah, it was
a waste of time,
but it was a lot
better than school.
It was not a waste of time.
I hate to break it to you, bro,
but, yeah, that's what it was.
You're an idiot.
Hey, shut up.
No, you shut up.
Hey, you want to go? Huh?
Hey, if you touch him,
I'll shove those sticks
down your throat, got it?
Mr. S. was cool. And we worked
too long and too hard
not to play this show.
Well, okay, so what are
we supposed to do?
I say we get out of here
and play the damn show.
How could you let
our children
be exposed to this
impostor, this maniac?
Do you just let anyone
walk off the street
and teach here?
(angry murmuring)
Let me assure you that nothing
is more important to us
than for you to feel
your children
are in a safe
and secure environment.
(angry murmuring)
(all talking at once)
Okay, we're all here
for the field trip.
Where's Mr. Schneebly?
He didn't tell you?
He's at his house.
We need to go pick him up.
Come on. Let's go, hurry.
Excuse me.
Just one second, please.
(angry murmuring)
Wait a minute,
wait a minute.
Where are you going?
(angry murmuring)
One second!
(door slams)
Where did they go?
Help!
Children!
(snoring, groans)
Wake up.
(groans)
How'd you guys get in here?
Front door was open.
Why aren't you guys
in school?
We did what you told us;
we stuck it to the man.
Forget about what I told you.
Look, I'm a loser, okay?
You listen to my advice,
you'll end up like me,
with nothing.
Come on, man,
quit goofing around.
This is serious business.
We're on a mission.
One great rock show
can change the world.
(horn beeps)
Look out the window.
(grunting)
Mr. S!
Come down!
No way.
That is so punk rock.
(mid-tempo rock beat plays)
The dining room table
seats 14, with no inserts...
What's going on?
We've got
some rocking to do.
(rock beat continues)
Yes!
All right.
Hi, Mr. Schneebly.
How's it going?
Whoo!
(cheering)
You guys, all
I can say is,
let's rock.
(cheering)
Yeah!
One more thing:
I want to say I'm sorry
that I used you guys.
I'm sorry I lied.
And it's not cool
to lie to your band.
Come on, we're going to be late.
There's no time for apologies.
Let's go, come on.
All right, let's go.
Where are you going?
I'm going to the show.
Do you want to go?
Yeah, I want to go.
Are you serious?
I don't want
to miss this, Patty.
Unbelievable.
After everything
he's done to you?
That is so "typical Ned."
When are you going to
stop being a pushover?
When are you finally
going to start
sticking up
for yourself?
(rock beat continuing)
Excuse me...
Excuse me.
I have just been informed
that all of your children
are missing.
So...
(angry murmuring)
(rock beat continuing)
Hey.
Hey. Can I help you?
Yeah, we're competing;
we're the School of Rock.
You and all these kids?
Yeah, we're the band and crew.
You'd better get in here,
hurry up.
Okay, come on, you guys.
Hey. We're here.
You're late.
You're up next.
Okay, we'll be ready,
come on.
Zack, check this out.
Whoa, it's awesome.
♪ Tears I can find on my own
♪ I'll take
♪ You there
♪ I'll never...
Guys, you don't have
to listen to those hacks.
Come on, band meeting
right now, gather round.
All right.
Frankie, how's security?
We're set.
Okay, Gordon,
what about the lights?
The light board is
up in the balcony.
I'll patch it up there.
All right.
And, Billy,
how's beautification?
Are you kidding?
Okay, listen up, you guys.
We only have one song to let
these guys know who we are,
so I think
we should play Zack's.
But why?
I mean, really?
Yes.
The thing is, you guys.
I ain't that good.
I'm not, and I can admit it.
But you, dude,
you're ten years old,
you're already better than me.
Your song rocks harder,
so let's play it.
But, hey, you know what?
That's just one guy's opinion.
This ain't my band,
it's our band.
We all have a say.
We haven't practiced
that one as much.
I mean, we might not win.
Hey, we didn't come here to win.
We came here to play
one great show.
And on Zack's song,
you guys really rock.
You know my vote,
who else is with me?
All right, let's pray.
God of Rock, thank you for this
chance to kick ass.
We are your humble servants,
please give us the power
to blow people's minds
with our high-voltage rock.
In your name we pray. Amen.
Amen.
Now let's get out there
and melt some faces!
Yeah!
Go get ready.
All right,
but you got to sing it.
Are you sure?
It's your song.
Yeah, it's cool,
I'm no singer.
Okay, I'll sing it.
Yeah?
What about the lights?
All the cues are
to the other song.
Okay, Gordon, you're just
going to have to feel it.
You've got to improvise.
You know this song,
I know you can do it.
Okay.
Go.
Run like the wind.
Hey. What's this?
You wanted to go with the
uniform, so put it on.
Quick.
♪ Hear my heartsick hungry cry
♪ I'm heartsick
♪ So heal me
♪ I'm hungry
But I can survive on ♪
♪ Hear my heartsick
Hungry cry... ♪
Whoa, slow down,
old man.
My son is in there.
Where's your ticket?
My son is in there;
he's ten years old.
I don't care
how old he is.
You're not getting past
me without a ticket.
We're not here to see the show.
Excuse me.
We have a situation here.
My name is Rosalie Mullins.
I am the principal
of Horace Green.
We had a field trip
that went awry.
Some lunatic has kidnapped
our kids, all right?
Our kids are in there.
Look, you guys are
breaking my heart.
There's the
ticket table.
All right, maybe we should
just get tickets.
All right,
let's get tickets.
(excited chattering)
Excuse me.
Excuse me, please.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
Our kids are in here.
Quit pushing!
Excuse me.
Hey, stop it.
Hey. What's up?
Uh...
(whistles)
Come on!
We're the School of Rock.
And this song was written
by our own Zack Mooneyham.
(electric guitar plays)
(rock chord plays)
(mid-tempo rock beat plays)
♪ Baby, we was making
Straight A's ♪
♪ But we were stuck
In a dumb daze ♪
♪ Don't take much
To memorize your lies ♪
♪ I feel like
I've been hypnoti-sized ♪
♪ And then that magic man
He come to town ♪
♪ Whoo-whee, he done
Spun my head around ♪
♪ He said recess is in session
♪ Two and two make five
♪ And now, baby
Oh, I'm alive ♪
♪ Oh, yeah!
I am alive ♪
♪ And if you want
To be the teacher ♪
♪ Ooh, la-la-la, ooh, la-la-la
♪ You just better forget it
♪ Rock got no reason
♪ Ooh, la-la-la, ooh, la-la-la
♪ You better get me
To school on time♪
♪ Oh, yeah!
Yeah!
(plays wild guitar solo)
♪ Oh, you know I was
On the honor roll ♪
♪ Got good grades
Ain't got no soul ♪
♪ Raise my hand
Before I can speak my mind ♪
♪ I've been biting my tongue
Too many times ♪
♪ And then that magic man
Took you away ♪
♪ Uh-huh
♪ Do what magic man do
♪ Not what magic man say
♪ Say what?
♪ Now can I please have
The attention of the class? ♪
♪ Today's ass-signment...
(clears throat)
(drums play)
♪ Kick some ass!
♪ And if you want
To be the teacher ♪
♪ Ooh, la-la-la, ooh, la-la-la
♪ You just better forget it
♪ Rock got no reason
♪ Ooh, la-la-la, ooh, la-la-la
♪ You better get me
To school on time ♪
♪ Ooh, la-la-la, ooh, la-la-la
♪ Well, baby, you just
Better forget it ♪
♪ Rock got no reason
Rock got no rhyme ♪
♪ You better get meto school
On time ♪
♪ Oh, yeah!
(music slows, softens)
(audience cheering, hooting)
♪ Oh, yeah!
(loud rock playing)
♪ This is my final exam
♪ Now y'all know who I am
♪ I might not be
The perfect son ♪
♪ But y'all be rocking
When I'm done ♪
(playing wild guitar solo)
(audience cheering)
Your son is
very skilled.
Thanks. So's yours.
(solo continues)
(screams)
(cheering)
Take me back!
Whoa.
Yeah!
(music ends)
(cheering)
(cheering continues)
School of Rock!
Woo!
(cheering)
Oh, sorry. To get in,
you've got to be
in a band
or have a pass.
I am principal
of the school's band.
Oh, right on.
All right? All right?
That was incredible!
That was incredible.
Oh, my gosh, the lights,
and the guitar solos...
Was it really you playing?
So you're not mad?
Mad? I'm furious.
I'm horrified,
but it was incredible.
It was so great.
You guys were so great.
(laughing)
Dude!
You did it, man.
Those lights were awesome!
They were awesome.
These kids are incredible.
Amazing.
Who's the manager?
SUMMER:
I am.
Summer Hathaway.
Nice to meet you.
Nice
to meet you.
Oh, hey, wait, stop.
Come here, guys.
You guys rocked, dude.
How old are you?
Ten. Ten?
No way, dude. How long you
been playing man?
About three years.
I used to play classical,
but now I play rock.
Hey, you in a band?
No. No.
No, I am the principal
of this school.
Yeah?
Yes.
Wow, that's cool.
That's cool.
Yes, yes it is.
It's very,
it's very cool.
Yeah.
Yes.
It is, cool.
It is.
It is very cool.
I like that.
Do you? Yes.
Yeah, you're hot.
You're so hot.
What?
Huh?
I'm sorry.
What?
Are you warm?
(cheering continues)
All right, guys, this is it.
The moment of truth.
The winner
of this year's
Battle of the Bands
competition...
...is No Vacancy.
(cheering)
DEWEY:
No! Boo!
It was a beauty contest.
They weren't even
listening to the music.
Boo! No!
What?
(murmuring)
Oh, no.
On behalf of
the Battle of the Bands,
I'd like to present this check
for $20,000 to No Vacancy.
Yeah!
No Vacancy!
No, School of Rock.
Come on!
School of Rock.
School of Rock!
What's wrong?
DEWEY:
Summer, didn't you hear? We lost.
Hey, chill out, dude.
Rock isn't about getting an A.
The Sex Pistols
never won anything.
Don't let
the man get you down.
Yeah, I mean, dude,
you got to cheer up.
We played
a kick-ass show.
We did, didn't we?
It was unbelievable, wasn't it?
Yeah.
School of Rock! School of Rock!
School of Rock!
What is that?
It's an encore.
They want us
to go play another song.
It's good! Go, you guys!
Wait, no, no.
Just the band.
Okay, everybody, go!
(cheering)
Thank you, yes,
we will play one more.
(bass tuning)
(cheering)
(AC/DC's "It's a Long Way
to the Top" begins)
♪ Riding down the highway
Riding down the highway
♪ Going to a show
♪ Stopping on the byway
♪ Playing rock and roll
♪ Playing rock and roll...
(engine putters)
Bye, Mom.
see you later.
I told you.
As soon as I talk to the band,
I'll get back to you.
If you're so desperate,
then quit low-balling us.
DEWEY:
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
Ah... mm-hmm.
Here we go.
♪ I tell you people
It's harder then it looks ♪
♪ 'Cause it's a long way
To the top ♪
♪ If you want to rock and roll
♪ Yes, it's a long way
To the top ♪
♪ If you want to rock and roll
Woo!
♪ You think it's easy
Playing one-night stands? ♪
♪ Well, try playing
In a rock and roll band ♪
♪ It's a long way to the top
♪ If you want
To rock and roll ♪
And that's a C.
All right? You got that?
Let's see.
Okay, Paula, lets see you?
Yeah, you're fingers
are... basically right.
Shawn, what
do you got?
Let's see.
All right, play.
Toby, you got it?
Let's see.
Very good
you guys.
♪ Getting gray
♪ Getting ripped off
♪ Underpaid
♪ Getting had
♪ Getting took
♪ I tell you, people
♪ It's harder than it looks
♪ 'Cause it's a long way
To the top ♪
♪ If you want to rock and roll
All right,
now take it down nice and quiet.
The next thing
I want to hear...
is a face-melting solo
by our own Zack Mooneyham, go.
Here we go!
(playing solo)
Woo!
Dude, is my face okay?
I think you
melted it off.
(laughs)
All right, now the next
thing I want to hear,
the very next thing--
I don't want to hear anything
unless I hear...
a gut-busting, drum solo
from Freddy.
Take it away!
(playing solo)
♪ Ah! It's a long way
To the top ♪
♪ If you want to rock and roll
♪ Yes, it's a long way
To the top ♪
♪ If you want to rock and roll
Aah! My gut got busted!
(laughing)
What did you do, Freddy?
Now, I think
it's time
we heard from a little somebody.
Lawrence on lead solo keyboard,
go!
(playing solo)
Woo!
♪ Long way to the top
♪ If you want to rock and roll
All right, slow it up.
Listen up, you guys.
Here's what I need.
I need you girls
to repeat after me.
♪ R-R-R-Roobee doobee doobee
♪ Roobee doobee doobee
♪ And blimbee blimbee blee
♪ Blimbee blimbee blee
♪ Chicka chicka chicka
Chicka chick chick ♪
chicka chick chick ♪
♪ Gah gah gah gah gee
All right.
Now the first test is over.
I'm going to need Alicia
to give me a two-second
vocal solo, go.
Here it comes.
♪ 'Cause it's a long way
To the top ♪
♪ If you want to rock and roll
♪ Oh, whoa, whoa
Don't Bogart
the mic, Alicia.
That was beautiful,
but now it's time.
Come on, Tomika,
melt it.
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh! ♪
That was tasty.
Marta, blow my brains out.
Go.
♪ The movie is over
♪ The movie's
Really over ♪
♪ But we're still on screen
♪ But we're still
On screen ♪
♪ Everybody's rocking
♪ And we came
From Horace Green? ♪
♪ We came from
Horace Green ♪
♪ Oh, yeah!
♪ It's time for my solo
(scatting)
♪ Woo! Woo! Woo! Woo!
(laughing)
♪ Movie's almost over
♪ Credits got to roll
♪ Look at that name there
♪ I do not know that guy
♪ Check it out now
♪ Get, get out
♪ Get him out
♪ It's time to go now
♪ It's time to go
♪ Other people got to come in
For the next show ♪
♪ You're getting in the way
♪ Getting in the way
♪ The cleaning guy
Is coming to clean up ♪
♪ The sticky stuff
On the floor ♪
♪ Ow!
♪ It's a long way
To the top ♪
♪ If you want to rock and...
Roll! ♪
♪ Yes, it's a long way
To the top ♪
♪ If you want
To rock and roll ♪
All right, that's it,
stop you guys, stop.
Seriously, you guys.
All right, take five.
(playing ends)
Take five.
You want to go?
All right.
That was a good class.
All right,
see you, man.